1
00:00:06,500 --> 00:00:09,000
About 2 months ago I found myself on
the comment section of YouTube

2
00:00:11,000 --> 00:00:17,000
And I was commenting,
unfortunately I was commenting,
on a video about the famous Ayn Rand

3
00:00:19,000 --> 00:00:24,000
And I
posted underneath against
this woman's tirades,
against what is essentially
the human race.

4
00:00:25,000 --> 00:00:31,000
that, this monetary system seems to have no point, seems to actually hinder people

5
00:00:31,000 --> 00:00:36,000
and hinder progress, and one of the responses I got, I didn't answer it, was:

6
00:00:37,000 --> 00:00:43,000
what actually money creates is an incentive to invent the new items, that's the driving force behind it

7
00:00:43,000 --> 00:00:50,000
So what I thought I do is instead if answering on a YouTube comment is organize a global awareness day

